All he needed was a lucky break. Then one day she moved in.
Vision Quest is a drama, romance film directed by Harold Becker.
After deciding he needs to do something meaningful with his life, high school wrestler Louden Swain sets out on a mission to
drop weight and challenge the area's undefeated champion, which creates problems with his teammates and health.
Matters are complicated further when Louden's father takes in an
attractive female drifter who's on her way to San Francisco.
Louden Swain, played by Matthew Modine.
Carla, played by Linda Fiorentino.
Larry Swain, played by Ronny Cox.
Margie Epstein, played by Daphne Zuniga.
The Coach, played by Charles Hallahan.
Kuch, played by Michael Schoeffling.
Vision Quest (released in the United Kingdom and Australia as Crazy for You) is a 1985 American coming-of-age romantic
drama/sports film starring Matthew Modine, Michael Schoeffling, Ronny Cox and Linda Fiorentino in her first film role.
It is based on Terry Davis's 1979 novel of the same name.
Modine plays a Spokane high school wrestler who falls in love with an older woman, an
aspiring artist from Trenton, New Jersey, on her way to San Francisco.
The film includes the first major motion picture appearance by Madonna, who plays a singer
at a local bar, where she performs the songs "Crazy for You" and "Gambler".
In some countries, the title of the film was changed to "Crazy for You" to capitalize
on Madonna's emerging fame and the popularity of her song of that name.
The film has become a cult classic.
The film explores themes of high school, sports, wrestling, wrestler, pizza.
The tone is emotional.